Guide to the Confederate Imprint collection, 1855-1879 MS 071
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Crandall Numbers; 1855-1867, 227678
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication from Secretary conveying information relative to the non-destruction of the cotton in the city of Savannah before its evacuation by our military forces, February 18, 1865; 228108 (Box 5, Folder C1324)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Communication of Secretary relative to the number of able-bodied men between the ages of eighteen and forty-five claimed to be exempt from conscription by the Governor, laws and resolutions of the State of Georgia, February 22, 1865; 228107 (Box 5, Folder C1327)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Correspondence between the Secretaries of War and the Treasury on the subject of a deficiency of funds, 1864; 228106 (Box 5, Folder C1330)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Correspondence... defenses of New Orleans 123p., March 11, 1863; 228105 (Box 5, Folder C1333)
  - C.S.A. Ordnance Bureau. Field Manual 149p., 1862; 228104 (Box 5, Folder C1340)
  - General Orders from Adjutant and Inspector-General's office, Confederate Army, from January 1862 to December 1863, 1864; 228103 (Box 5, Folder C1343)
  - C.S.A. Adjutant and Inspector-General's Office. General Orders from the Office, Confederate States of America, for the year 1863, with a full index. Compiled and corrected under authority of Gen. S. Cooper, A. and I.G. By H.P. Robinson, 1864; 228102 (Box 5, Folder C1344)
  - General Orders from the Adjutant and Inspector-General's Office, Confederate Army, from January 1 to June 30, 1864, 228101 (Box 5, Folder C1345)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. General orders. Adjutant and Inspector-General's Office. No's 1, 100, January 1, December 8, 1862; 228100 (Box 5, Folder C1348)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. General orders. Adjutant and Inspector General's Office. Nos. 1-48, 50-127, 129-136, 138-164, January 3, 1863-December 29, 1863; 228099 (Box 5, Folder C1349)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. General orders. Adjutant and Inspector-General's office nos. 27, 30, 39, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 57, 58, 67, 73, 82, 83, 87, 1864; 228098 (Box 6, Folder C1350)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. General orders. Adjutant and Inspector-General's Office nos. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 11, 1865; 228097 (Box 6, Folder C1351)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Letter from the secretary of war, March 31, 1862; 228096 (Box 6, Folder C1358)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Letter of the secretary of war, enclosing a copy of the official report recently made by Colonel Imboden, 1863; 228095 (Box 6, Folder C1362)
  - C.S.A War. Dept. Letter of Secretary of War conveying information relative to the amount of money expended in the payment of the Army of the Trans-Mississippi since the assignment of Gen. E.K.Smith to the command, Dec. 8, 1864; 228094 (Box 6, Folder C1363)
  - C.S.A. Army, Department of Tennessee, Official Report, Battle of Chickamauga 234p., 1864; 228093 (Box 6, Folder C1372)
  - Confederate States. Official Reports of Battles. Richmond, 1864; 228092 (Box 6, Folder C1375)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Official report of battles... Vicksburg and Baton Rouge 170p., 1863; 228091 (Box 6, Folder C1379)
  - The Ordinance Manual for the Use of the officers Of the Confederate Army 546p., 1863; 228090 (Box 6, Folder C1383)
  - Bloomfield, B. The Quartermaster's Guide 113p., 1862; 228089 (Box 6, Folder C1387)
  - Regulations for the Army of the Confederate States, 420p., 1862; 228088 (Box 6, Folder C1390)
  - Regulations for the Army of the Confederate States, 420p., 1862; 228087 (Box 6, Folder C1391)
  - Regulations for the Army of the Confederate States, 420p., 1863; 228086 (Box 6, Folder C1393)
  - Regulations for the Army of the Confederate States with a full index ,432p., 1864; 228085 (Box 6, Folder C1396)
  - Regulations for the Army of the Confederate States Revised and enlarged, 1864; 228084 (Box 6, Folder C1397)
  - Regulations for the Army of the Confederate States and for the Quartermaster's and Pay Departments 100p., 1861; 228083 (Box 6, Folder C1399)
  - Regulations for the Subsistence Department of the C.S.A. 56p., 1861; 228082 (Box 6, Folder C1408)
  - Regulations for the Subsistence Department of the Confederate States 54p., 1862; 228081 (Box 6, Folder C1409)
  - Quartermaster's Regulations 182p., 1864; 228080 (Box 6, Folder C1411)
  - C.S.A. Ordnance Dept. Regulations, 1861; 228079 (Box 6, Folder C1412)
  - Report of Gen. Ripley 42p., 1864; 228078 (Box 6, Folder C1416)
  - C.S.A. Army Dept. of Northern Virginia. Report Operations at Rappahannock Bridge, 1864; 228077 (Box 6, Folder C1420)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Report Battle of Helena, 1864; 228076 (Box 6, Folder C1421)
  - C.S.A. Army, Dept. of Mississippi. Report Battle of Baker's Creek, 1864; 228075 (Box 6, Folder C1423)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Report of the Secretary of War, Dec.14, 1861; 228074 (Box 6, Folder C1425)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Report of the Sec. 33p., Nov.26, 1863; 228073 (Box 6, Folder C1430)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Report of the Sec. 37p., April 28, 1864; 228072 (Box 6, Folder C1431)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Report of the Sec., Nov. 3, 1864; 228071 (Box 6, Folder C1432)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Report of Thomas W. Wagner of the sinking of the stone fleet at the entrance of Charleston Harbor, 1862; 228070 (Box 6, Folder C1433)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Response of Sec. to the Resolution of the Senate, adopted Dec. 5th 1864 respecting operations under the act of 6h February 1864, Dec. 10, 1864; 228069 (Box 6, Folder C1436)
  - C.S.A. War Dept. Supplemental report of the Sec. of War, March 17, 1862; 228068 (Box 6, Folder C1444)
  - Alabama. Acts of the Called Session of the General Assembly of Alabama held in the city of Montgomery, January 1861; 228067 (Box 7, Folder C1456)
  - C.S.A. Alabama. General Assembly. Acts of 2nd Called Session 303p., 1861; 228066 (Box 7, Folder C1457)
  - Acts of the Called Session 1862 and of the General Assembly of Alabama (2 copies), October 27, 1862; 228065 (Box 7, Folder C1459)
  - Acts of the Called Session of 1863 and of the General Assembly of Alabama, August 17, 1863; 228064 (Box 7, Folder C1461)
  - C.S.A. Florida Tallahassee Convention. Journal 112p., January 3, 1861; 228063 (Box 7, Folder C1499)
  - Florida. Proceedings of the Convention of the people of Florida at called sessions, begun and held at the Capital in Tallahassee, February 26, 1861 and April 18, 1861; 228062 (Box 7, Folder C1502)
  - Florida. The acts and resolutions adopted by the General Assembly of Florida at its eleventh session, begun and held at the Capital, Tallahassee on November 18, 1861, 1862; 228061 (Box 7, Folder C1503)
  - Florida. The acts and resolutions adopted at the 1st session of the 12th General Assembly of Florida, begun and held in Tallahassee, November 17, 1862; 228060 (Box 7, Folder C1504)
  - Florida. Senate journal. Journal of the proceedings of the Senate of the General Assembly, of the State of Florida, at the thirteenth session, November 21, 1864; 228059 (Box 7, Folder C1509)
  - Journal of the Proceedings of the House of Representatives of the General Assembly of the State of Florida at the 11th Session, November 18, 1861; 228058 (Box 7, Folder C1510)
  - Florida. House Journal-13th Session. A journal of proceedings of the House of Representatives of the General Assembly of the State of Florida, at its 13th session, November 21, 1864; 228057 (Box 7, Folder C1513)
  - Journal of the Public and Secret Proceedings of the Convention of the People of Georgia held in Milledgeville and Savannah, 1861; 228056 (Box 7, Folder C1518)
  - Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Georgia passed in Milledgeville at an Annual Session in November and December 1861, 1862; 228055 (Box 7, Folder C1521)
  - Georgia. General Assembly. Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Georgia, passed in Milledgeville, at an annual session in November and December, 1862; also extra session of 1863, 228054 (Box 7, Folder C1522)
  - Georgia. General Assembly. Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Georgia passed in Milledgeville, at an annual session in November and December, 1863; also extra session of 1864, 228053 (Box 7, Folder C1523)
  - Georgia. General Assembly. Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Georgia, passed in Milledgeville, at an annual session in November, 1864; also extra session of 1865, at Macon, 228052 (Box 7, Folder C1524)
  - Georgia. Laws, Statutes, etc. Public Laws, 1861; 228051 (Box 7, Folder C1525)
  - Georgia, Laws, Statutes, etc. Public Laws, 1863; 228050 (Box 7, Folder C1528)
  - Georgia. General Assembly. Papers relative to the mission of Hon. T. Butler King to Europe, 1863; 228049 (Box 7, Folder C1538)
  - Georgia. General Assembly. Senate. Journal of the Senate at an extra session of the General Assembly of the State of Georgia, convened under the proclamation of the Governor, March 25, 1863; 228048 (Box 7, Folder C1541)
  - Georgia. General Assembly. Senate. Journal of the Senate at an extra session of the General Assembly of the State of Georgia convened under the proclamation of the Governor, March 10, 1864; 228047 (Box 7, Folder C1543)
  - Georgia. Governor Jos. E. Brown Message, 1864; 228046 (Box 7, Folder C1569)
  - [Preamble and resolutions passed by the mayor and Council of the city of Atlanta] (photocopy), 1861; 228045 (Box 7, Folder C1607)
  - C.S.A. Army. Lewis' Brigade Resolutions [Mounted Infantry, Kentucky], 1865; 228044 (Box 7, Folder C1612)
  - Proceedings of the Louisiana State Convention (in English and French) together with the Ordinances, 1861; 228043 (Box 7, Folder C1613)
  - Acts Passed by the Fifth Legislature of the State of Louisiana at its Second Session, January 21, 1861; 228042 (Box 7, Folder C1617)
  - Acts Passed by the Sixth Legislature of the State of Louisiana at its First Session, November 25, 1861; 228041 (Box 7, Folder C1618)
  - Saint Landry Parish. Ordinance... Police of Slaves 29p., 1863; 228040 (Box 7, Folder C1652)
  - Mississippi. Convention 1861. Journal of the State Convention and Ordinances and resolutions adopted in January, 1861. Also inserted after p.220 with title: Statement showing assessment of personalty in the State of Mississippi, together with number of acres and value of taxable lands for year 1860, last page missing, 228039 (Box 8, Folder C1654)
  - Mississippi. Convention 1861. Journal of the State Convention and ordinances and resolutions adopted, March 1861; 228038 (Box 8, Folder C1655)
  - Laws of the State of Mississippi passed at a called session of the state legislature, July 1861; 228037 (Box 8, Folder C1659)
  - Laws of the State of Mississippi passed at a regular session of the state legislature, Novemberand December, 1861 and January, 1862; 228036 (Box 8, Folder C1660)
  - Laws of the State of Mississippi passed at a called and regular session of the State Legislature, December 1862, November 1863; 228035 (Box 8, Folder C1661)
  - Journal of the Convention of the People of North Carolina, May 20, 1861; 228034 (Box 8, Folder C1699)
  - North Carolina. Executive and legislative documents. Session 1862-1863. Doc. No. 21, Letter of the president of the Chatham Railroad, 228033 (Box 8, Folder C1789)
  - North Carolina. Executive and legislative documents. Extra sessions 1863-1864, 228032 (Box 8, Folder C1791)
  - North Carolina. Private laws of the State of North Carolina, passed by the General Assembly at its session of 1860-61, 1861; 228031 (Box 8, Folder C1795)
  - North Carolina. Public laws of the State, passed by the General assembly at its session of 1860-61: together with the Comptroller's statement of public revenue and expenditure, 1861; 228030 (Box 8, Folder C1802)
  - General Assembly. North Carolina. Public laws passed at 2nd extra session 140p., 1861; 228029 (Box 8, Folder C1803)
  - North Carolina. Public laws of the state of North Carolina, passed by the General Assembly at its adjourned session of 1862-63, 1863; 228028 (Box 8, Folder C1805)
  - North Carolina. Public laws of the State of North Carolina, passed by the General Assembly at its called session of 1863, 228027 (Box 8, Folder C1806)
  - South Carolina Convention documents, special committee of 21 181p., 1862; 228026 (Box 8, Folder C1871)
  - Journal of the Convention of the people of South Carolina held in 1860-61, 1861; 228025 (Box 8, Folder C1880)
  - South Carolina Convention (2 copies, one flat, one rolled), 1860; 228024 (Box 8, Folder C1887)
  - South Carolina Genearl Assembly. Acts of the General Assembly of the state passed in September and December 1863, 1864; 228023 (Box 8, Folder C1901)
  - South Carolina. Governor (Pickens) Correspondence relating to the Post Office, 228022 (Box 8, Folder C2098)
  - South Carolina, Governor (Pickens). The governor's message and correspondence with the commissioners from Virginia, 228021 (Box 8, Folder C2099)
  - South Carolina Governor (Pickens) Message No.1, 1862; 228020 (Box 8, Folder C2104)
  - South Carolina Auditor report... slaves, 1864; 228019 (Box 8, Folder C2112)
  - South Carolina Commissioners Correspondence 26p., 1861; 228018 (Box 8, Folder C2122)
  - South Carolina. Dept. of the Military Report, 1862; 228017 (Box 8, Folder C2127)
  - Unthank, J.H. and Hebb, George S. Digest of Militia Laws of Tenn., 1861; 228016 (Box 8, Folder C2138)
  - Regulations adopted for the Provisional Force of the Tennessee Volunteers, together with the act of Tennessee legislature of 1861 organizing said provisional force, 228015 (Box 8, Folder C2146)
  - Texas. Committee on Public Safety Reports, 1861; 228014 (Box 8, Folder C2167)
  - Address to the Texan soldiers in the C.S.Army (photocopy), 1863; 228013 (Box 8, Folder C2170)
  - Texas. General laws of the ninth Legislature of the state of Texas, 1862; 228012 (Box 8, Folder C2171)
  - General Laws of the tenth legislature of the state of Texas, 1864; 228011 (Box 8, Folder C2173)
  - General laws of the tenth legislature (called session) with the provisional permanent constitutions of the Confederate States, 1864; 228010 (Box 8, Folder C2174)
  - General laws of the tenth legislature (second extra session) of the state of Texas, 1864; 228009 (Box 8, Folder C2175)
  - Laws of the eighth legislature of the State of Texas (extra session), 1861; 228008 (Box 8, Folder C2179)
  - Message of Gov. Houston, of Texas, on secession (photocopy and typed copy), 1861; 228007 (Box 8, Folder C2193)
  - Texas Governor Edward Clark. Proclamation to the people of Texas... (2 photocopies), August 26, 1861; 228006 (Box 8, Folder C2209)
  - Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Virginia passed at called session, 1862; 228005 (Box 8, Folder C2256)
  - Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Virginia passed at adjourned session, 1863; 228004 (Box 8, Folder C2273)
  - The New Constitution of Virginia with the amended Bill of Rights as adopted by the Reform Convention of 1850-51 and amended by the Convention of 1860-61, 1861; 228003 (Box 8, Folder C2274)
  - Addresses Delivered before the Virginia State Convention by Hon. Fulton Anderson, Hon. Henry L. Benning, and Hon. John S. Preston, February 1861; 228002 (Box 8, Folder C2257)
  - C.S.A. Official Documents no.1-54, February 1861-April 1861; 228001 (Box 9, Folder C2258)
  - Virginia. Ordinance to repeal ratification of the constitution of the U.S. Broadside (photocopy), 1861; 228000 (Box 9, Folder C2262)
  - Virginia Convention. Rules and Articles... Army of Virginia, 1861; 227999 (Box 9, Folder C2264)
  - Virginia Convention. Ordinances, 1861; 227998 (Box 9, Folder C2263)
  - Ordinances and Acts of the Virginia Convention, 1861; 227997 (Box 9, Folder C2271)
  - Acts of the General Assembly of Virginia passed in 1861-2, 1862; 227996 (Box 9, Folder C2272)
  - Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Virginia passed at called session 1863, 227995 (Box 9, Folder C2275)
  - Acts of the General Assembly of the State of Virginia passed at the general session 1863-1864, 227994 (Box 9, Folder C2276)
  - Address of the General Assembly to the Soldiers of Virginia (photocopy), 1864; 227993 (Box 9, Folder C2277)
  - Message of the Governor of Virginia and Accompanying Documents, January 1861; 227992 (Box 9, Folder C2278)
  - Message of the Governor of Virginia and Accompanying Documents, December 1861; 227991 (Box 9, Folder C2279)
  - Board of Public Works (turnpikes) Documents, 1861; 227990 (Box 9, Folder C2279.17)
  - Board of Public Works (railroads) Documents, 1861; 227989 (Box 9, Folder C2279.17)
  - Message of the Governor of Virginia and Accompanying Documents, 1862; 227988 (Box 9, Folder C2281)
  - Virginia General Assembly. Called session 1863, doc.no.1, Message of the Governor of Virginia, 227987 (Box 9, Folder C2282 #1)
  - Virginia General Assembly. Committee on Confederate Relations Report, 1864; 227986 (Box 9, Folder C2282 #31)
  - Virginia. Laws, statutes, etc. Sketches of the Acts..., 1861; 227985 (Box 9, Folder C2285)
  - Virginia. Laws, Statutes etc. Sketches of The Acts..., 1864; 227984 (Box 9, Folder C2286)
  - Virginia Senate Journal and Documents Extra Sessions 1862 and 1862-3, 1863; 227983 (Box 10, Folder C2296)
  - Virginia Senate Journal and Documents Extra Session 1863, 227982 (Box 10, Folder C2297)
  - Virginia Senate Journal and Documents Session 1863-4, 1864; 227981 (Box 10, Folder C2298)
  - Virginia Journal and Documents of the House of Delegates 1861, 227980 (Box 10, Folder C2356)
  - Journal of the Virginia House of Delegates Called Session 1862, 1863; 227979 (Box 10, Folder C2359)
  - Documents of the Virginia House of Delegates Called Session 1862, 1863; 227978 (Box 10, Folder C2360)
  - Journal of the Virginia House of Delegates Called Session 1863, 227977 (Box 10, Folder C2361)
  - Documents of the Virginia House of Delegates Called Session 1863, 227976 (Box 10, Folder C2362)
  - C.S.A. Army. Wise's Brigade. Resolutions of Wise's Brigade, 1865; 227975 (Box 10, Folder C2377)
  - Andrews, R. Snowden. Andrews' Mounted Artillery Drill Compiled According to the Latest Regulations, 1863; 227974 (Box 10, Folder C2392)
  - Brown, William Leroy. Notes on Artillery, 1862; 227973 (Box 10, Folder C2397)
  - Buckholtz, L.V. Infantry Camp Duty, Field Fortification and Coast Defence, 1861; 227972 (Box 10, Folder C2399)
  - Buckholtz, L.V. Tactics for Officers of Infantry, Cavalry and Artillery, 1861; 227971 (Box 10, Folder C2400)
  - Bugeaud de la Piconnerie, Thomas Robert, due d'Isly. The Practice of War; being a translation..., 1861; 227970 (Box 10, Folder C2401)
  - Cary, R. Milton Skirmishers' Drill and Bayonet Exercise 48p., 1861; 227969 (Box 10, Folder C2402)
  - Cooper, Samuel. Cooper's Cavalry Tactics, 1861; 227968 (Box 10, Folder C2406)
  - Curry, John P. Volunteers' Camp and Field Book, 1862; 227967 (Box 10, Folder C2408)
  - Davis, J. Lucius, The Trooper's Manual: or, Tactics for Right Dragoons and Mounted Riflemen (2 copies), 1861; 227966 (Box 10, Folder C2409)
  - Fowler, W.H. Guide for Claimants of Deceased Soldiers, 1864; 227965 (Box 10, Folder C2413)
  - Gilham, William. Manual of Instruction for the Volunteers and Militia of the Confederate States, 1861; 227964 (Box 10, Folder C2418)
  - Gilham, William. Manual of Instruction for the Volunteers and Militia of the Confederate States, 1862; 227963 (Box 11, Folder C2419)
  - Hardee, W.J. Rifle and Infantry Tactics (volumes 1 and 2), 1863; 227962 (Box 11, Folder C2429)
  - Hardee, W.J. Rifle and Infantry Tactics, 1862; 227961 (Box 11, Folder C2430)
  - Lee, C.H. The Judge Advocate's Vade Mecum: Embracing a General View of Military Law, 1863; 227960 (Box 11, Folder C2441)
  - Lee, J.K. The Volunteer's Handbook: Containing an Abridgement of Hardee's Infantry Tactics, adapted for the use of the Percussion Musket in Squad and Company Exercises, Manual of Arms for Riflemen, 1861; 227959 (Box 11, Folder C2445)
  - The School of the Guides, for the Use of The Army of the Confederate States with Questions, 1862; 227958 (Box 11, Folder C2451)
  - Mahan, D.H. A Treatise on Field Fortification, containing instructions on the methods of laying out, constructing, defending, and attacking intrenchments, 1862; 227957 (Box 11, Folder C2459)
  - Marmont, Marshal. The Spirit of Military Institutions. Trans. Frank Schaller, 1864; 227956 (Box 11, Folder C2462)
  - Napoleon's Maxims of War, 1862; 227955 (Box 11, Folder C2463)
  - Nolan, L.E. Cavalry; Its History and Tactics, 1864; 227954 (Box 11, Folder C2464)
  - Pardigon, C.F. Infantry Sword Exercise, 1863; 227953 (Box 11, Folder C2465)
  - Richardson, Jno. H. Infantry Tactics, or, Rules for the Exercise and Manoeuvres of the Confederate States Infantry in the Evolutions of the Line, compiled, arranged and adapted to Hardee's Drill, 1862; 227952 (Box 11, Folder C2469)
  - Richardson, Wm. H. A Manual of Infantry and Rifle Tactics, with Honors paid by the Troops, 1861; 227951 (Box 11, Folder C2471)
  - Roberts, Joseph. The Hand-Book of Artillery for the service of the United States (Army and Militia), 1862; 227950 (Box 11, Folder C2475)
  - The Ordnance Manual for the Use of the Officers of the United States Army, 1861; 227949 (Box 11, Folder C2488)
  - Wheeler, Joseph. A Revised System of Cavalry Tactics for the Use of the Cavalry and Mounted Infantry, C.S.A., 1863; 227948 (Box 11, Folder C2491)
  - Legion Francaise; New Orleans. Ordre de Jour, 1861; 227947 (Box 11, Folder C2516)
  - Letter from the Ladies of the South. Broadside (photocopy), 1862?; 227946 (Box 11, Folder C2518)
  - Parker. Sufferings of the Twelfth Georgia Regiment (photocopy), 1862?; 227945 (Box 11, Folder C2534)
  - Special Instructions for the Government of the Guard... Broadside (photocopy), 1864; 227944 (Box 11, Folder C2547)
  - To the Southern Rights Men of Harrison County. Broadside (photocopy), 1861; 227943 (Box 11, Folder C2554)
  - Wadsworth, George. Camp McDonald, The School of Instruction... (photocopy), 1861; 227942 (Box 11, Folder C2556)
  - Cooke, John. The Life of Stonewall Jackson from Official Papers, Contemporary Narratives, and Personal Acquaintance, 1863; 227941 (Box 11, Folder C2563)
  - Dabney, Robert L. True Courage... Jackson, 1863; 227940 (Box 11, Folder C2568)
  - Hoge, Wm.J. Sketch of Dabney C. Harrison, 1863; 227939 (Box 11, Folder C2582)
  - Life of James W. Jackson, 1862; 227938 (Box 11, Folder C2590)
  - Ramsey, James B. True Eminence in Jackson, 1863; 227937 (Box 11, Folder C2600)
  - White, William Spottswood. Sketches of the Life of Capt. H.A. White of the Stonewall Brigade, 1864; 227936 (Box 11, Folder C2610)
  - Barde, Alexandre. Histoire des Comites de Vigilance aux Attakapas, 1861; 227935 (Box 11, Folder C2614)
  - Battle of Fort Sumter, 1861; 227934 (Box 11, Folder C2615)
  - Clarke, H.C. Diary of the War for Separation 191p., 1862; 227933 (Box 11, Folder C2618)
  - Davis, Nicholas A. The Campaign from Texas to Maryland, 1863; 227932 (Box 11, Folder C2621)
  - Marginalia; or Gleanings from an Army Note-Book, 1864; 227931 (Box 11, Folder C2623)
  - Harris, W.A. Record of Ft. Sumter, 1862; 227930 (Box 11, Folder C2628)
  - Hurst, M.B. History of the 14th Ala.Vols.(2 copies), 1863; 227929 (Box 11, Folder C2630)
  - Jacskon, Henry W.R. Historical Register..., n.d.; 227928 (Box 11, Folder C2633)
  - Jackson, Henry W.R. The Southern Women of the second American Revolution 120p., 1863; 227927 (Box 11, Folder C2634)
  - Jones, Charles C. Monumental Remains of Georgia. Part 1 119p., 1861; 227926 (Box 11, Folder C2635)
  - Keily, Anthony M. Prisoner of War, or Five Months Among the Yankees 120p., 1865; 227925 (Box 11, Folder C2637)
  - Pollard, Edward A. The First Year of the War, 1862; 227924 (Box 12, Folder C2643)
  - Pollard, Edward A. The First Year of the War: Corrected and Improved Edition, 1862; 227923 (Box 12, Folder C2645)
  - Pollard, Edward A. Observations in the North: Eight Months in Prison and On Parole, 1865; 227922 (Box 12, Folder C2647)
  - Pollard, E.A. Rival Administrations: Richmond and Washington 31p., 1864; 227921 (Box 12, Folder C2648)